What about three player games like 3-player isolation?
那三人游戏呢 比如三人孤立棋？
&gt;&gt; What's 3-player isolation?
三人孤立棋是什么？
&gt;&gt; It's the same as normal isolation, but
和普通孤立棋一样
with three players trying to be the last to move.
不过有三个玩家比赛谁能走到最后
&gt;&gt; So do the players form alliances against each other?
所以三个玩家之间会组成联盟来对抗另一方吗？
&gt;&gt; They can, but there can be only one winner in the end.
可以的 但最后只能有一个赢家
&gt;&gt; That could make the evaluation function difficult.
这会让评估函数变得很麻烦啊
&gt;&gt; Why don't we ignore that for now and just #my_moves to make things simple?
我们何不先忽略这一点 先用函数 #my_moves 把事情简化来看看？
How would minimax work?
要怎么用极大极小值算法呢？
&gt;&gt; Well, for multiplayer games we don't use minimax anymore.
对于多人游戏 我们不用极大极小值算法了
Instead, we evaluate the game board from the perspective of each player and
我们要从每个玩家的视角出发来评估棋局
propagate the values up the tree.
然后将分值向博弈树上方传递
&gt;&gt; How does that work?
要怎么做？
&gt;&gt; Let's a imagine a three player isolation game tree,
想象一棵涉及三个玩家的孤立棋博弈树
where we search down to the level three of the tree.
我们搜索到了博弈树的第三层
On the leftmost branch,
在最左边的分支上
we evaluate the resulting game board from each of the players' perspectives.
我们分别从各玩家的视角出发 对棋局进行评估
For player 1, the evaluation function returns a 1.
对玩家 1 来说 评估函数返回值为 1
For player 2, it's a 2.
玩家 2 返回值为 2
And for player 3, the evaluation is a 6.
玩家 3 返回值为 6
&gt;&gt; I guess we evaluate each of the board nodes at this level, and
我猜我们要评估这一层的每个棋局节点
then return triplet's for each of them.
然后返回出相应的三元组
&gt;&gt; Yep, and then we propagate the values up the tree.
对的 然后将分值向树的上方传递
We first choose the max value at each of the level 2 branches
我们先为第二层每个分支取最大值
from the player 3's perspective.
从玩家 3 的视角出发来选
In the leftmost node, player 3 has a choice between 6 and
在最左边的节点上 玩家 3 可以在 6 和
3, so, of course, we choose 6.
3 之间选 所以我们当然选 6 了
In the next branch from the right on that level,
往右数第二个分支
there's a choice between a 2 and a 1, so we chose 2.
可以在 2 和 1 之间选 所以我们选 2
In the third branch from left, we choose between a 2 and a 1, so we choose the 2.
然后往右数第三个分支 我们要在 2 和 1 之间选 所以选 2
And, finally, in the rightmost branch, we choose the 5.
最后 最右边的分支选 5
Okay and for the next level up,
好了 接着向上一层
I guess we choose the maximum value from player 2's perspective?
我们要从玩家 2 的视角出发来选最大值？
&gt;&gt; Yep. &gt;&gt; So
对的 所以
on the left branch we choose the branch with the 2,
在左边的分支里 我们选有 2 的这个分支
and on the right branch we chose the 5.
然后右边的分支我们选 5
&gt;&gt; Precisely, and
就是这样
at the top level we choose the maximum value from player 1's perspective.
到了最高层 我们从玩家 1 的视角出发来选最大值
In this example, both options are equally good, so
这个时候 选择都一样
we choose the one on the left by default.
所以我们默认选左边的
This version of a game tree, which we call a Max N, can work for
这种博弈树叫作 MaxN
multiplayer games with any number of players.
适用于多人游戏 无论有多少玩家都适用
&gt;&gt; Let's try a quiz on this concept. 最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6
学完这个概念 我们来做做练习吧. 最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6